<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Han and the Telescreen</title>
    <link>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Han and the Telescreen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Han</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:01:12 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Imitation Game</title>
      <link>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/big_idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/big_idea/</guid>
      <description>Han Zhong Stephen Mack Writing 340 15 October 2022
&amp;ldquo;Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic&amp;rdquo;, said Arthur C. Clarke, the famous science fiction writer. This statement is especially true in the field of artificial intelligence. In recent years, we have seen AI beating human champions at game of Go. We have seen them creating art and winning prizes. There&amp;rsquo;s even an essay written by AI published on The Guardian, trying to convince us that &amp;ldquo;robots come in peace&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Code</title>
      <link>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/health_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 04:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/health_code/</guid>
      <description>To have complete control over their subject is the dream of all rulers through out history. Tighter control over people could mean better military power, stronger economy, and more stable society. More than 2000 years ago, when ancient China is dominated by the Seven Warring States， emperors of Qin state established a system that grouped households by 5. Each group must report any crimes committed by members of the group and failure to report crimes would result in execution of everyone in the group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI is coming to get you ... but not in the way you think</title>
      <link>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/ai/</guid>
      <description>In the 2017 documentary AlphaGo, the AI researchers at DeepMind complained that, the news media often associate their ground breaking AI Go player with killer robots like the Terminator. They think this association contributes to the public&amp;rsquo;s irrational fear of their work on artificial intelligence. Their frustration is very understandable since DeepMind&amp;rsquo;s AlphaGo couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more different from the Terminator. For starters, AlphaGo doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like Arnold Schwarzenegger and couldn&amp;rsquo;t turn itself into liquid metal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have you tried turning the internet on and off again?</title>
      <link>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 04:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/internet/</guid>
      <description>The Iranian government has been repeatedly shutting down the internet since September 19 in an effort to control the antigovernment protests. As crazy as it seems, it&amp;rsquo;s not the first time such a restriction of internet connectivity happens. In fact, it has become quite a common practice for authoritarian regimes to limit internet access to counter a protest or a potential one. Last February, during the military coup in Myanmar, a decrease in local internet connectivity has been reported by many global internet traffic monitor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great American Joke</title>
      <link>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/public_intellectual/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 23:54:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/public_intellectual/</guid>
      <description>Since the 70s, the American public&amp;rsquo;s confidence in news media and the government has been on a steady decline. It&amp;rsquo;s almost natural that something like The Daily Show (TDS) would come out of this time of distrust to ridicule these rotting institutions. In the beginning when TDS just premiered at Comedy Central, it was a simple comedy show that uses news format only as a framing for the jokes. After the original host Craig Kilborn left the show in 1998, Comedy Central found Jon Stewart, at the time a leather-jacketed Gen X wisecracker famous for his hip MTV talk show, to take over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 14:54:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughtp0lice.github.io/my_blog/posts/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello world</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
